Ramin Beiramzadegan

professional summary

First of all, a graduate with a great deal of work experience to carry out a diversity of professional settings. Following graduation, and outside of my studies, I have a large number of skills, including extraordinary levels of communication and flexibility; by this way, I am able to hang out with all type of people whether strict or easygoing. Furthermore, I am a hardworking person and well-adapted and I can ideally be suited to large companies with graduate recruitment programs. Lastly, I am keenly interested in following my dreams, desires and my goals as well to achieve them leading to come true as soon as possible.

zafre.bahrami@gmail.com

00989123476484

unit 6 no1 VALA residential building SINA dead end 24 METRY blvd SAADAT ABAD street, Tehran, Iran

0

EDUCATION

Articulated bachelor's degree Islamic Azad University of Pardis

2013 – 01/2016

computer engineering

Tehran

• GPA: 16.18 out of 20

Continuous associate degree Islamic Azad University of Karaj

2005 – 07/2008

GPA: 12.47 out of 20

Кагај

Diploma

Sanaye Iran technical high school

2003 – 2004

Computer science

GPA: 17.02 out of 20

Tehran

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end programmer & Ui/Ux programmer Positive - Negative

10/2012 – Present designing and web development

Contact: us@pnidea.com

software and network troubleshooting Emdad Rayaneh Parto Gostar Modiriat

05/2011 – 09/2012

computer software and hardware troubleshooting

Tehran,Iran

Tehran.Iran

Contact: Info@Emdadrayanehco.com

database intern & developer

Bahar Net

09/2008 – 03/2011 web and mobile app development Tehran,Iran

Contact: Info@Baharnet.ir

recommendation professors names and emails in order:

Assistant professors

- Mohamad Fadaeian
- parisa rahmani

Contact: Fadaeian@pardisiau.ac.ir – Rahmani@pardisiau.ac.ir

SKILLS

movie editor

computer troubleshooting

database developer

web programming

fluent on English speaking

pre_intermediate level on French speaking

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Asian Archery Federation (10/2011 – 10/2011)

Interpreter

Mui Thai competitions (09/2012 - 09/2012)

Interpreter

GR & FS Wrestling World Cup (02/2013 - 02/2013)

Interpreter

FS World Wrestling Clubs Cup (11/2014 - 11/2014)

Interpreter

CERTIFICATES

Python programming (2019 – 2019)

LANGUAGES

English

French

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Limited Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

music player: I have played Piano for a few years, Santoor (traditional musical instrument) for 7 years, Tombak (traditional musical instrument) for many years

studying English literature since i was 14 or studying other languages which i am keenly interested in. watching movies, going to cinema and listening to musics

studying books related to technology and science

playing some sports including billiard professionally , football, and fitness sports, chess, swimming